My Spidey sense tells me
this has something to do with Penny.
Look, do you wanna buy me out or not?
I'll give you $100, which will make me
half-owner, and we'll put it on my balcony.
(Howard:)Screw his balcony.
I'll give you 120 and put it in my garage.
- I paid $200 for my share.
- Everybody knows a time machine loses...
(Raj:)...half its value the minute
you drive it off the lot.
I'll go for 200.
That time machine stays right where it is.
(Raj:)Three hundred. And I'll throw in my original
1979 Mattel Millennium Falcon...
...with real light-speed sound effects.
(Leonard:)No. No more toys or action figures
or props or replicas...
(Leonard:)...or costumes or robots
or Darth Vader voice changers.
(Leonard:)I'm getting rid of all of it.
(Howard:)You can't do that.
Look what you've created.
(Howard:)It's like Nerdvana.
(Raj:)More importantly,
you have a Darth Vader voice changer?
- Not for long.
- I call dibs on the Golden Age Flash.
(Howard:)I need that to complete
my Justice Society of America collection.
(Raj:)- I called dibs.
- You can't.